jinni.com 2015-03-23

# Find movies, TV shows matching your taste and watch online - Privacy Policy

Jinni Media Ltd. ( **'Jinni'** , **'we'** or **'us'** ) respects the privacy of the users ( **'User'** or **'you'** ) of its Site at [www.jinni.com](http://www.jinni.com/) and/or App (as such terms are defined in detailed in our Terms of use at [www.jinni.com/info/terms.html](http://www.jinni.com/info/terms.html) (the **'TOU'** )), and is fully committed to protect the personal information that its Users share with it. We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we may collect and use when you use our Site and/or our App. Capitalized terms which are not defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in the TOU, which this Privacy Policy is incorporated thereto by reference. 

## Your Consent (PLEASE READ CAREFULLY!)

BY INSTALLING THE APP, ENTERING TO, CONNECTING TO, ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE AND/OR APP YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THE **'PRIVACY POLICY'** ), INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITE AND/OR APP, AND YOU MAY NOT INSTALL THE APP AND PROMPTLY ERASE THE APP AND ANY PART THEREOF, FROM YOUR MOBILE PHONE AND DO NOT USE IT IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVE. 

## Which information we may collect on our Users?

We may collect two types of data and information from our Users:

  1. The first type of information is non-identifiable and anonymous information **('Non-personal Information')**. **We are not aware of the identity of the User from which we have collected the Non-personal Information**. Non-Personal Information is any unconcealed information which is available to us while Users are using the Site and/or App. Non-personal Information which is being gathered consists of technical information and behavioral information, and may contain, among other things, type of mobile device and operating system, type of browser, screen resolution, number of stamps, places users have stamped, etc.
  2. The second type of information is individually identifiable information **('Personal Information')**. **This information may identify an individual or may be of a private and/or sensitive nature.**  

    * Users of the Site and/or App automatically provide their IP address mainly for enhancing the User's experience and for geolocation and security purposes as further detailed below.
    * Users who are interested in using our Services via the Site can choose to stay anonymous. However, Users who wish to receive Special Services (as such term is defined in the TOU) must open an Account. Users who are interested in using our Services via the App must register and open an Account.
    * Users who are interested in opening an Account in order to use our App and/or Services should provide details via the registration form on the Site and/or within the App, i.e username, and e-mail address. The User may also provide, at his/her sole discretion, his/her image and date of birth.
    * Alternatively, Users can open an Account and signup to the Service via existing third party accounts (namely, Facebook account) used by the User. Namely, in the event that a User registers to the Site and/or the App through his/her existing third-party web account (namely, the User's Facebook account), then such third-party website provides us, per our request, with certain information about such User as is stored in such third-party account, namely, the User's image, his/her name, e-mail address, date of birth, age, gender, preferences on movies and TV shows, the User's friends and the friends' preferences on movies and TV shows.
    * Jinni may require additional Personal Information in order to provide you with additional features you may be interested in. For example, your location and service provider are needed to tell you which movies are on TV or in theaters near you.
    * In the event that the User is interested in importing his/her ratings from other websites such as Rotten Tomatoes, etc. then such User should provide us with his/her log-in information to such websites.

For avoidance of doubt, any Non-Personal Information connected or linked to any Personal Information shall be deemed as Personal Information as long as such connection or linkage exists.  
 **We do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you without your approval, which is obtained, inter alia, through your active acceptance to the Terms and the Privacy Policy.**

## How Do We Collect Information on Our Users?

There are two main methods we use:

  1. **We collect Non-Personal Information through your use of the Site and/or App.** In other words, when you are using the Site and/or App we are aware of it and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage, either independently or through the help of third-party services as detailed below.
  2. **We collect Personal Information which you provide us voluntarily.** We collect Personal Information when you register and open an Account by either completing the registration form or by registering through a third-party account (namely, Facebook). When registering through a third-party account, you agree to grant Jinni access to Personal Information stored in the third-party account, as detailed above. We store the Personal Information either independently or through the help of our authorized third-party service providers as detailed below.

## What are the Purposes of the Collection of Information?

Non-personal Information is collected in order to:

  * Create aggregated statistical data for research purposes (for example to show average ratings for titles) and customization and improvement of the Site and/or Service and/or the App.
  * Enhance your experience on the Site and/or the App and help us determine which content interests the Users.

Personal Information is collected in order to:

  * Operate the Service (including, inter alia, provide personalized entertainment and better personalized recommendations.
  * Be able to contact Users for the purpose of providing them with technical assistance and support and collect feedback regarding the Service.
  * Reply to your online queries made through the Site and/or the App.
  * Determine general geolocation information (i.e., country) from which the User's computer or mobile device is connected to the Internet in order for us to know the general location of our Site's and/or App's Users as well as in order to safeguard our Site and our App.

## Sharing Information with Third Parties

Jinni will share Personal Information it collects to the extent the disclosure is required for providing the Services. Mainly, subject to your Display Options (as detailed below) Jinni displays the Users' Personal Information on their Account and elsewhere on the Site and/or the App. This information can be seen by all visitors of the Site and User's of the App. Jinni may also discloses Personal Information in the following cases: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy and/or the TOU, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to User's support requests; (e) respond to claims that any content available on the Site and/or the App violates the rights of third-parties; (f) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party had been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (g) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Jinni, its Users, or the general public; (h) when Jinni is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of its assets; (i) to collect, hold and/or manage your Personal Information through Jinni's authorized third party service providers (for example, Amazon cloud services), as reasonable for business purposes, which may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction; or (j) pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure. For avoidance of doubt, Jinni may transfer and disclose 

_Non-personal Information_

to third parties at its own discretion. 

## Display Options

The default settings for your Account allow us to display to others the User's Personal Information everywhere on the Site and/or the App. To edit such default settings, you can login to your Account, click on 'Settings' and choose that your Account will be 'private'. 

## Entertainment Personality

From the moment you create your Account and provide feedback such as ratings, likes and check-ins, Jinni generates an Entertainment Personality for you, and begins offering you personal recommendations, as well as group recommendations for you and your friends. We refine your Entertainment Personality by following your activities on the Site and/or App, including how you rate titles, which titles you decide to watch, and what you recommend to others. This information is intended to improve your recommendations and taste matches. Jinni does not process any Personal Information related to your viewing preferences and/or profile in any other way. However, note that, subject to your Display Options, any other User can see your activity meter (a measure of your overall activity level on the Site and/or App), your Entertainment Personality description and your taste compatibility with other Users. 

## Minors

To enjoy the Service, you must be over the age of thirteen (13). Therefore, Jinni does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) and does not wish to do so. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under the age of thirteen (13) are not using the Service. 

## Links to Third Party Websites

In the event of a merger, acquisition or reorganization of Jinni ownership, user information will likely be a part of the assets transferred. An acquiring company may substantially change this privacy policy. Jinni will endeavor to notify all users of any such changes. 

## Modification or Deleting Personal Information

If for any reason you wish to update, modify or delete your Personal Information you may do so on the Site and/or the App by clicking the 'Settings' option or by contacting us using the means offered on the Site and/or App. Once you request to delete your account we shall delete all personal information within a reasonable time pursuant to any applicable privacy laws. Note that unless you instruct us otherwise we may retain your Personal Information for a period of ninety (90) days or a longer period as required to provide you with the Services. 

## Direct Marketing and Advertisements

Direct Marketing: You hereby agree that we may use your contact details for the purpose of informing you regarding products, services and new features (offered by Jinni) which may interest you, and to send to you advertisements and other marketing material, transmitted to the e-mail address you have provided.

You may withdraw your consent via sending a written notice to Jinni by email to the following address: [info@jinni.com](mailto:info@jinni.com) or on the same manner as the advertising was transmitted to you.

Advertisements: We accept advertisements from third party advertisers. These advertisers are carefully selected to provide information about products and services that we think may be of interest to our Users. Note that if you click on any of these advertisements, these advertisers may use cookies and other web-tracking technologies to collect non-personal and/or personal information about you. We recommend that you review the terms of use and privacy policy for any advertiser with which you are interacting before doing so. Their privacy policy, not ours, will apply to any of those interactions. 

## Security

We take a great care in implementing and maintaining the security of the Jinni Site, App and our Users' Personal Information. The Personal Information is hosted on the Amazon Cloud which provides advanced security features. Jinni employs industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of its Users' Personal Information, and prevent unauthorized use of any such information. However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur. 

## Third Party Software/App

While using the Site and/or App we may be using third party software and/or App, in order to collect, store and/or process the information detailed herein. Such software/App include without limitation, Google Analytics which privacy policy can be found at: <http://www.google.com/analytics/> and Amazon cloud services which privacy policy can be found at: <http://aws.amazon.com/privacy/>. 

## Cookies

When you access or use the Service, the Company may use industry-wide technologies such as 'cookies' (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer **('Local Storage')** and which will allow us to enable automatic activation of certain features, and make your Service experience much more convenient and effortless. The cookies used by the Service are created per session, does not include any information about you, other than your session key and are removed as your session ends. It is easy to prohibit the Local Storage. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer's hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies your online experience may be limited. 

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the Site and App and any information collected therein. Jinni reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will provide notice of substantial changes of this policy on the homepage of the Site and/or on the App and/or we will send you an e-mail regarding such changes to the e-mail address that you provided in the registration form. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on our Site and/or App or sent by email. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated 'Last Revised' date and your continued use of the Site and/or the App after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes. 

## Have any Questions?

If you have any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, you are welcome to send us an email at: [info@jinni.com](mailto:info@jinni.com) and we will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timeframe.
